localvideoacademy.com 2016-06-11

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. To manage your personal data or unsubscribe, please contact us via email at support@localvideoacademy.com.

For each visitor to our web page, our web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

As stated in our Terms and Conditions and The Earnings Disclaimer, we collect the phone number, postal address, and credit card numbers for our paying customers. We also collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our web page. Your information will never be sold to any outside party.

We collect aggregate data on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information from the pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, and name, address, and telephone number.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web page, customize the content and/or layout of our page, notify consumers about updates to our website, track consumer preferences, enhance the consumer experience, and contact consumers for marketing purposes. We may also use this information for marketing and promotional purposes, as well as statistical analysis.

To safeguard your information, we use third-party software to securely collect payments, maintain our customer contact information, and host our websites. All online transactions are encrypted. For the purpose of authorization and completion of transcations, information you submit when making an online purchase is shared with payment processors and your credit card company.

We disclose information when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, or in a transfer to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, or other corporate changes respecting the website. We will not intentionally disclose your personal information to any third party without your express permission, except as otherwise stipulated in this policy.

If you divulge personal information online through discussion boards or forums, you do so at your own risk. Information disclosed online through discussion boards and forums is subject to collection by third parties and we are unable to guarantee the protection of that information.

We use browser cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, and to record past site activity. Browser cookies also enhance navigation of our website and enable specific processes. You may choose to disable cookies on your browser, however that may limit access and usability.

Any websites that appear as links through our site are governed by a separate privacy policy which should be reviewed before submitting your personal information.

By using our website, you expressly consent to the terms described in this Privacy Policy. We are committed to maintaining the security and integrity of your personal information.

 **CONTACT INFORMATION:**  
Brandon Lucero  
support@localvideoacademy.com  
 **BML Media Group, LLC © 2016**
